Who are you? It's outside of visiting hours.
你是谁？已经过了访客时间了
I am Draht, a servant
我是多拉特
and executioner of Aura the Guillotine.
是断头台阿乌拉的手下与斩首吏
I'm here to kill you.
我是来杀你的
I see. You're done playing diplomat?
这样啊 外交游戏已经玩完了？
It's just beginning.
才刚开始而已
Just to let you know, I'm strong.
话先说在前头 我可是很强的
Stronger than me?
比我强吗？
Stronger than Aura the Guillotine.
比断头台的阿乌拉强
-That's hard to believe. -Why?
-我没办法相信耶 -为什么？
Because it's already over for you.
因为已经结束了
A wire made of mana, huh? That's interesting magic.
用魔力构成的线？还真是有趣的魔法
You concentrated mana around your neck and stopped it from slicing?
将魔力集中在颈部来防止被断头吗？
You're pretty calm.
还真是冷静呢
Any other mage would've been decapitated without realizing a thing.
换做其他魔法使 可能连头怎么掉的都不知道
However, this wire is one of the strongest among demon magic.
不过这可是 魔族的魔法中最强韧的一种线
Human magic cannot do anything about it.
人类的魔法根本拿它没办法
I will slice right through your mana.
我会把你的头连同魔力一起斩断
I agree, I don't think I can do anything about this wire.
我同意 我认为我也拿这条线没办法
He thinks he won with just this, huh?
你已经确信自己赢定了？
This generation of demons is no good.
这一代的魔族真是不怎么样呢
They're inexperienced in actual combat.
实战经验太少了
She…
她…
cut my arm!
切断了我的手！
You bitch--
臭女人…
Wait! Let's talk--
等等 我有话…
One down…
先解决一个了
If I report this assault to the Graf and take care of the other two,
如果跟伯爵报告这次的袭击 把剩下那两只也解决掉的话
I'm sure I'll be granted amnesty.
应该可以获得赦免吧
The guard is dead…
卫兵死了…
ORIGINAL STORY BY KANEHITO YAMADA / TSUKASA ABE
（原作：山田钟人 作画：阿部司）
This is delicious.
这个好好吃
Master told me that
师父说过
a town with good food is a peaceful, good town.
有美食的城市 就是能安居乐业的好城市
That probably applies here.
那套理论一定可以用在这里吧
-Master Stark. -You can't have this.
-休塔尔克大人 -这个才不给你
Let's appeal directly
我们直接去
to Graf Granat and have him release Mistress Frieren.
找古拉纳特伯爵 请他放了芙莉莲大人吧
It's only a matter of time until this town is harmed.
这座城受到危害只是时间早晚的问题
Let's get Mistress Frieren out of prison and have her take down the demons.
把芙莉莲大人从牢里放出来 让她去打倒那些魔族吧
I guess that's our only choice.
确实也只能这么做
We're no match for them.
我们根本不是他们的对手
Especially that guy named Lügner. He's ridiculously strong.
尤其是那个叫做琉古纳的家伙 他可不是普通的强悍
He was only looking at Frieren.
他那时只看着芙莉莲一个人
Even though you and I and the guards were around…
就算旁边有你跟我 还有那些卫兵在…
he was only looking at Frieren.
他眼里只看着芙莉莲
Because to him, he can kill us anytime.
因为对他而言 要解决我们根本易如反掌
My hands are still shaking.
我的手到现在还在抖
See? It spilled and now it looks like I wet myself.
你看 都洒到裤子了 看起来就像我吓尿了
That's how scary he is.
那家伙就是这么可怕
Hurry up and wipe yourself, please. We have to go.
请快点擦干净 我们要走了
Lügner is going to be near the Graf.
琉古纳会在伯爵身边吧
It might lead to combat.
很可能会打起来
The party of heroes would still have gone.
如果是勇者一行 他们还是会去的
You're right. If I shrink back now,
你说得没错 如果我现在就畏畏缩缩
I won't be able to face my master.
以后就无法面对师父了
Let's go!
走吧！
You can have that handkerchief.
那条手帕你就留着吧
-What's wrong? -It's making me weak at the knees.
-怎么了？ -我吓到腿软了
I can't detect Draht's mana.
感知不到多拉特的魔力了
He must be dead.
一定是死了
What a fool. He let his guard down.
真是笨蛋 他轻忽大意了
Let his guard down?
轻忽大意？
We serve as Mistress Aura's right hand.
我们可是阿乌拉大人的左右手
We're executioners.
是斩首吏
Do you think we'd die just by letting our guard down?
你认为我们会 因为一时的轻忽大意而丧命？
Who is that mage?
那个魔法使到底是谁？
Sorry to make you wait.
抱歉让你们久等了
The mage we captured escaped prison.
昨天抓到的魔法使逃狱了
She cut off the guard's head.
她砍掉了卫兵的脑袋
That must be troublesome.
那一定很麻烦吧
I will help in the search.
我也来帮忙搜查吧
-Linie excels in mana detection-- -No, that's not necessary.
-里尼厄对于魔力感知很在行… -不必 不需要
By the way, you seem to be missing one person.
话说回来 你们好像少了一位同伴
He's using the restroom. He'll be back shortly.
他去卫生间了 很快就会回来
Without asking a servant where it is?
都不用问过位置就去了？
Even I could tell that mage is highly skilled.
就连我都看得出来 那名魔法使不简单
Yet she was easily captured by the guards.
然而面对卫兵时 她却轻易地束手就擒
She knows how serious of a crime it is to kill a guard.
她很清楚杀掉卫兵是多重的罪
Lord Lügner, I will ask you one more time.
琉古纳殿下 我再问你一次
Where is your companion?
你的同伴在哪里？
My goodness…
真是的
That good-for-nothing Draht.
多拉特那个废物
He ruined everything.
让一切努力都白费了
But strangely enough,
但还真是奇怪呢
this blasted situation that leaves us
这种让我们不得不
with no option but to use violence
动用武力的糟糕局面
brings me irresistible joy.
却让我不由得高兴起来
Graf Granat, what are "words"?
古拉纳特伯爵 语言到底是什么？
What makes it different from this sword?
这把剑究竟哪里与众不同？
No matter what you use, the weak will always die.
不管你用什么东西 弱者必死无疑
Just like the owner of this sword.
就跟这把剑的主人一样
Lügner!
琉古纳！
In the end, we're nothing but beasts.
说到底 我们毕竟还是猛兽
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
不用担心 我不会杀了你
You will help us remove the defense barrier of this town.
你还得给我们 解除这座城市的防护结界
We're almost at the Graf's mansion.
就快到伯爵宅邸了
Mistress Frieren?
芙莉莲大人？
Aren't you Mistress Frieren?
是芙莉莲大人吧？
Why are you here?
你怎么在这里？
Don't tell me you escaped?
别告诉我您越狱了
I had no choice.
我也是没有办法啊
While I was in prison, some demon named Draht attacked me.
我在牢里的时候 有个叫做多拉特的魔族跑来攻击我
I defeated him, but…
虽然是击杀他了 不过…
demons become mana particles and disappear when they die.
魔族死后 就会变成魔力分子 然后消失殆尽
What about that?
那有什么问题吗？
He had killed the prison guard.
他杀了看守监狱的卫兵
All that was left at the scene
现场只留下了
was a guard that was beheaded by magic
被魔力斩首的卫兵
and me, a mage.
还有身为魔法使的我
How do you view this situation?
你怎么看待这种状况？
You'll be sentenced to death for killing a guard.
您会因为杀死卫兵被判处极刑
Right? It's too much of a hassle so I'll leave town.
是吧？那太麻烦了 所以我要出城
Please wait.
请等一下
The remaining demons will roam free.
这样不就会放任 剩下的魔族四处游走吗？
Are you going to abandon this town?
您要对这座城市袖手旁观吗？
You two can take them down.
你们去打倒他们不就好了？
Don't make it sound so easy.
别说得那么容易
We're no match for them.
我们根本不是他们的对手
You won't fight them because they're strong?
难道因为对方很强就不战斗了？
Plus, I don't think
还有 我啊
for a second that you two are weaker than those demons.
可从没认为你们比那些魔族来得弱喔
Wait up! We'll fight them!
等等啊 我们会去战斗！
So please help us, at least! I'm begging you!
所以至少帮帮忙嘛！我都跪下来了！
Peek…
偷看一下…
Wait, please!
拜托别走啊！
-Please, Frieren! -Don't be stubborn.
-拜托啦 芙莉莲！ -你就放弃吧
-Let's face reality. -No way…
-面对现实吧 -哪有这样的…
-It's impossible. -Stop whining.
-打不赢的 -别抱怨了
About ten kilometers from town, I'm guessing.
离城里大概十公里左右吧
That's an immense amount of mana.
有股庞大的魔力在那里
Waiting to see our next move, huh?
那边在观望这里的动静吗？
Aura the Guillotine, one of the Seven Sages of Destruction.
大魔族七崩贤之一 断头台阿乌拉
I hate fighting strong opponents too, you know.
我也讨厌面对强大的敌手
It's best to get your least favorite tasks over with first.
讨厌的事情最好早点解决
Is it okay
不要紧吗？
that we're sneaking in like this?
我们这样偷偷溜进来
Do you want to tell the gatekeeper that we're here to kill the messenger of peace?
难道你想告诉门卫 我们是来刺杀和谈使者的？
It's eerily quiet.
安静得出奇呢
I love magic.
我对魔法很着迷
The famous Elder Sage of Corruption, Qual…
就像那位腐败贤者古瓦尔…
Just as he spent most of his life
将自己人生大部分的时间
developing a spell to kill humans…
都用来开发杀死人类的魔法
Within our long lifespan, we, demons,
我们魔族终其一生
dedicate our entire lives to researching one kind of magic.
都会倾注生命时光 致力于研究一种魔法
Over a long period of time, we pursue it day after day.
在这样漫长的岁月里 日复一日地精益求精
In ten years, our magic will be far superior to now
十年后 我们的魔法 会远比现在更精良
and our power will be even more unwavering.
我们的力量会更加强大
However, magic can be very funny.
然而 魔法也很不可思议
Like the defense barrier,
比如大魔法使伏拉梅
which keeps demons out and protects this town,
这种能阻止魔族入侵
made by the Great Mage Flamme.
保护这座城市的防御结界
Magic that a genius created a thousand years ago
千年前的魔法天才所创造的魔法
can still surpass modern magic.
仍然可以超越当今魔法
I hate geniuses.
我讨厌天才
They lack the beauty of accumulated effort.
他们少了那种日积月累的美感
The management of the barrier has been passed down
而防护结界世世代代
through the Granat family.
都由古拉纳特家族掌管
The fact that demons like us were able to enter the town
既然我们这种魔族可以进入城市
means that there must be a spell that controls the barrier.
就表示一定有控制结界的魔法
Tell me what that is.
把那种魔法告诉我
Maybe I'll give you some time.
也许我该多给你一点时间
Think hard about it.
好好想想吧
Making people wait is an effective
让对方等待是人类之间
diplomatic strategy among humans, right?
有效的外交手段吧？
If you don't tell us, all that awaits you is more torture.
你要是不说 我们多的是折磨你的方法
There must be a grimoire about barriers somewhere.
跟结界有关的魔导书 一定就在这里的某个地方
Check the bedroom. I'll search the study.
你去卧室找 我去书房看看
Oh, you're the adventurer brat from this afternoon.
什么嘛 你是今天 下午那个冒险者小鬼
I thought my son came to take me to the afterlife.
我还以为是我儿子来接我了呢
You're in horrible shape. They would go this far?
真惨 有必要做到这种地步吗？
I'll get you out right away.
我马上带你出去
-You're trembling. -Do you have a problem?
-你在发抖 -有意见吗？
No, you're courageous.
没有 你很勇敢
My dead son was trembling before he went to battle too.
我死去的儿子 上战场之前也一样在发抖
Damn! I can't cut the rope. Is it magic or what?
该死 绳子弄不断 这是魔法做的吗？
Forget about me.
不用管我了
I won't make it anyway.
反正我也活不久了
More than that, get the townspeople to evacuate.
更重要的是撤离城里的居民
None of them will listen to us if you're not there anyway.
你要是没有出现 也不会有人听我们的话
The Granat family's emblem is around my neck.
古拉纳特家族的家徽就挂在我脖子上
If you show this to the guards, they will listen to whatever you say.
卫兵们看到这个 你说什么他们都会听令于你
One more thing, you brat.
还有一件事 臭小鬼
Using informal speech with me is a serious crime in this town.
跟我说话这样没大没小 在这座城里可是重罪
That's right. If you go now, I'll let you off the hook.
那样就对了 你现在走的话 我就放你一马
-Hurry up and go. -Is that right.
-快走吧 -是这样吗？
Sorry, old man.
抱歉了 大叔
I'm going to break this fancy chair.
我要毁了这把贵重的椅子
I can't pay for damages though!
虽然我应该赔不起就是了…
Master Lügner, there's a rat.
琉古纳大人 有老鼠
Graf Granat, is he an acquaintance?
古拉纳特伯爵 他是你认识的人吗？
No, he's one of the adventurers from this afternoon.
不是 他是今天下午 那群冒险者其中一人
He probably came to negotiate with me not knowing
他八成不知道他同伴已经越狱了
that his comrade already escaped prison.
还跑来找我协商放人
What a dumb kid.
真是个笨小子
I see.
这样啊
Again…
又来了…
You may leave, kid.
小朋友 你可以走了
-I'll let you off the hook. -There it is again.
-这次就放你一马 -又来了
He won't even look at me.
这家伙看都不看我一眼
What's wrong? Move out of the way.
怎么了？快滚开
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
你敢碍我的事 我就杀了你
Try it then.
那你试试啊
He's fast.
好快
But he's just a human after all.
但终究是个人类
You guarded your vitals, huh?
守住要害了？
Your reflexes aren't bad.
反应不错嘛
But I guess all youths are rash no matter if you're a demon or human.
看来不管是魔族还是人类 年轻人一样都很冲动呢
You're thoughtless and reckless.
思虑不周又太过鲁莽
However, I will acknowledge your valor for standing up against me alone.
不过 你只身一人 对抗我的勇气值得嘉许
Alone?
只身一人？
I see… So you really can't see, huh?
这样啊 果然你们看不到吧？
Excuse me?
你在说什么？
Fern, I created an opening just as you ordered.
菲伦 我按你的要求争取时间了
Master Lügner, I detect a mage.
琉古纳大人 我感知到有魔法使
That can't be… A mere human mage was able to
不可能…明明是人类魔法使
get past Linie's mana detection unnoticed?
里尼厄的魔力感知怎么侦测不到？
And this spell is…
还有这个魔法是…
-Master Lügner, I will handle this. -Stop.
-琉古纳大人 这里交给我 -住手
Girl, what is this spell?
小姑娘 这是什么魔法？
Ordinary offensive magic.
一般攻击魔法
If I remember correctly, in your framework of magic
如果我没记错的话 在你们的魔法体系里
it is called Zoltraak.
这叫做“杀人魔法”
You call this Zoltraak?
你称它为“杀人魔法”？
Don't be ridiculous.
少说蠢话了
Us demons overcame Zoltraak more than half a century ago.
我们魔族早在半世纪以前 就已经克服杀人魔法了
Who taught you this spell?
是谁教你这种魔法的？
You're just buying time, aren't you?
你只是在争取时间吧？
I will finish you off.
得赶快解决你
I won't let you.
休想得逞
Fern!
菲伦！
The Graf's injuries are severe.
伯爵的伤势很严重
We don't have time to fight. Let's retreat.
没时间打了 撤退吧
Yes.
好
As soon as I stop bleeding, we'll go after them. You take the warrior.
等我止血完 我们就去追他们 战士由你负责
My blood is on both of them.
他们身上都沾到我的血
I won't lose track of them.
不会追丢的
There's no need for you to kill them yourself, Master Lügner.
不用琉古纳大人亲自出马
I'll take care of the mage too.
魔法使也交给我解决吧
If you were hit by her magic you would have died.
刚刚如果是你被打中 你就必死无疑
That spell was modified to specialize in killing demons.
这是专门为了杀死魔族而改良的魔法
You cannot call it Zoltraak anymore.
已经不能叫做“杀人魔法”了
It's a spell to kill demons.
这是用来杀死魔族的魔法
That girl's movements seemed familiar.
那个小姑娘的身手看起来很面熟
I have been hit by that same spell before.
以前我曾经被同样的魔法击中过
I see…
原来如此…
I remember now.
我想起来了
It's Frieren.
是芙莉莲啊
She greatly helped humans in their research and analysis of Zoltraak.
她在人类研究分析 杀人魔法这一块有巨大的贡献
The mage who has killed the most demons in all history.
史上葬送过最多魔族的魔法使
Frieren the Slayer.
葬送的芙莉莲
Another genius that I hate.
是另一个我讨厌的天才
Master Lügner is going to be mad.
琉古纳大人会发火的吧
This is crazy.
这也太扯了
-Any demon can do it. -I am at an advantage.
-是魔族都能办到 -我占了上风
Let's try together.
一起加油吧
"Aura the Guillotine."
断头台阿乌拉
Subtitle translation by: Kiko Morita
字幕翻译：洪贞韵